<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<workHistory>
	<job>
		<company>AZCO Corp.</company>
		<position>Graphic Designer | Feb. 2014 - 2015</position>
		<description>
			Develop strategic designs according to business and brand specifications to further aid the marketing and sales department. Duties include taking photos and videos, photo editing, creating tear sheets and collaborating with others, uploads to website and the creations of flyers and banners.
		</description>
		<location>Fairfield, NJ, USA</location>
	</job>

	<job>
		<company>Fried Arts</company>
		<position>Freelance Designer | Aug. 2009 - 2015</position>
		<description>
			Responsible for the production of print and web materials for clients while producing innovative designs and products. Consultation of design choices and development. Experiments on 3D designs, video editing and flash animations.
		</description>
		<location>Freelance, USA</location>
	</job>


	<job>
		<company>Raine Magazine.</company>
		<position>Graphic Designer | Aug. 2013 - Jan. 2014</position>
		<description>
			Help in the aid and development of the fashion magazine “RAINE” catered to the entrepreneur by means of digital design and occasional marketing materials. Common tools used - InDesign, Illustrator and Photoshop. Freelance position for friedarts.
		</description>
		<location>Freelance, USA</location>
	</job>


	<job>
		<company>MyPublisher INC.</company>
		<position>Graphic Designer | May 2012 - July 2013</position>
		<description>
			Develop strategic designs according to business and brand specifications and contribute to brainstorms and high-concept meetings to develop innovative designs. Also, Using illustrator help aid in the development of card and book productions in a SVG format for our desktop applications. In addition, communicate with developers to reach deadlines accurately.
		</description>
		<location>New York City, NY, USA</location>
	</job>

	<job>
		<company>Subway LLC</company>
		<position>Kitchen Prep | Nov. 2011 - May 2012</position>
		<description>
			Help establish a Subway start-up in Newport Mall, Jersey City, NJ by aiding in the preparation of foods such as onions, lettuce, pepper and baking of Subway’s signature bread. Also, occasionally aid as a sandwich artist or cashier using the POS system.
		</description>
		<location>Jersey City, NJ, USA</location>
	</job>

	<job>
		<company>The Destruction Company</company>
		<position>General Helper | Aug. 2011 - Nov. 2011</position>
		<description>
			Help an underground start-up in facility maintenance and idea development. Occasionally, I was in charge of moving or organizing objects or anything having to do with repairs of our local office.
		</description>
		<location>Hoboken, NJ, USA</location>
	</job>

	<job>
		<company>Delicias De Puerto Rico</company>
		<position>Waiter | Jan. 2011 - May 2011</position>
		<description>
			Aid in the establishment of a Puerto Rican restaurant as a waiter. Ensure the satisfaction of each client and servicing their needs. Additional duties included window washing, bussing, processing payments and general maintenance of the restaurant.
		</description>
		<location>Jersey City, NJ, USA</location>
	</job>

	<job>
		<company>Pearance LLC</company>
		<position>Web Dev. Intern | Oct. 2010 - Jan 2011</position>
		<description>
			Aid in the development of infrastructure for startup with the use of GIMP and Oracle Virtual Box. Assist in the development and/or assistance of files and documentation of sites using HTML/CSS and PHP in addition to providing consultation for our clients.
		</description>
		<location>Jersey City, NJ, USA</location>
	</job>
</workHistory>